所以这是一个我经常得到的问题。
So this is a question I get a lot.
我在推特上或在人们谈论和快乐的时候都能得到一个顿号
I get a ton on Twitter or
people talking about and happy hour.
他们说如果我没有经验，怎么办 ?
They say what do I do if I
have little to no experience?
你有什么建议
Now, what would you recommend?
我们都是从某个地方开始的
We all started somewhere.
这是我们共同分享的一件事。
That is one thing we all share.
我们都是从某个地方开始的
We all started somewhere.
你是怎么在第一个工作的门口找到你的脚的
How did you get your foot in
the door at the first job?
任何人，这是一个公开的问题。
Anybody, this is an open question.
是吗 ?
Yeah?
>> I 已应用于 QA 位置。
&gt;&gt; I applied to a QA position.
然后我就把我的方式变成了一个发展的位置。
And then I kind of worked my way
into more of a development position.
那是我的工作
That worked for me.
> > 这条路很棒
&gt;&gt; That's a great path.
我甚至都没考虑过
I didn't even think of that, yeah.
如果您在 UI 中没有经验，是否有人会将您作为 UI 工程师?
If you have no experience in UI,
is someone gonna you as a UI engineer?
也许吧也许吧
Maybe, maybe.
但另一种方法是应用不同的角色和
But is another way of just applying for
a different role and
你会怎么做呢
then working your way into that?
那是一个非常有效的角色。
That's a very effective role.
我见过人们自己做的
I've seen people do it themselves.
从办公经理到 QA 销售到 QA 工程师。
Move from office manager
to sales to QA to engineer.
为什么不呢 获得新工作的最简单方法是
Why not?
The easiest way to get a new job is to
留在你的公司继续走着去或者上下移动
stay at your same company, just keep
moving sideways, or move up or down,
不管你想要什么
wherever you want.
真是太棒了
That's a great tip.
怎么了
Yes?
>> 在早期我就知道每个人都会利用我
&gt;&gt; In the early days, I just knew
everybody was gonna take advantage of me,
所以我就建了一堆地方给当地企业，就像
so I just built a bunch of sites for
local businesses and just like for
在成本方面的方式。
way under cost.
但是，未来的人们不知道那些人付出了多少。
But then, the future people didn't
know how much those people paid.
所以我要给他们一个更公平的价钱
So I would charge them a more fair
price and every time getting money for
下一个项目。
the next project.
>> 那就好了 > > 刚开始就开始了
&gt;&gt; That's a good-
&gt;&gt; I started with just getting
利用。
taken advantage of.
>> [LAUGH] >> 但最终仅收费
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; But then, eventually just charged
更高更高的价格直到我得到真正的报酬
higher and higher prices until
I was getting really good pay.
>> 你们俩有我还没有想到的建议。
&gt;&gt; You two have suggestions
I didn't even think of yet.
是的开始在那边自由了
Yes, start out freelancing on the side.
低税率有人会雇你
Charge low rates, someone will hire you.
我会说一个关于自由职业的警告
I'll say a warning about freelancing.
不像你想的那么迷人
It's not as glamorous as you may think.
你就像我很酷的代码我每天都能制造新的东西
You're like I do cool code and
I get to build something new every day and
人们为此付出代价
people pay me for that.
不像任何有自由舞的人都会告诉你
No, as anybody who has
freelanced will tell you,
这不一定是很愉快的
it's not necessarily that pleasant.
但如果你找到合适的人
But if you find the right person,
正确的客户你可以一起工作
the right client,
you can really work together.
如果他们说这个人是个好工程师
And if they say this person's
a good engineer, you're like well,
我在找工作
I'm looking for steady work.
你被雇用了
You're hired.
我们不需要采访你我们见过你所做的工作
We don't have to interview you cuz
we've seen the work you have done.
这条路要走的路很棒
That's a great path to getting in if
你没有那么多专业经验
you don't have that much
professional experience.
> > 它主要是一个结束的手段。
&gt;&gt; It's s mostly a means to an end.
> 嗯，这就是一个很好的例子。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, that's a great example.
有什么建议吗
Any any other suggestions?
这些都很好
These are good.
这些都是我一直想知道的问题。
These are questions that
I get all the time.
这些都是很有帮助的。
So these are really helpful.
我知道很多人说你应该有一个强大的 GitHub ，有一大堆的例子。
I know a lot of people say you should have
a robust GitHub with a ton of examples.
你应该去
Yeah, you should.
但这不会让你被人发现的
But that's not gonna help
you get noticed by anybody.
你可能觉得人在不停地拖 GitHub for wow，这个人的
You may think people are constantly
trolling GitHub for wow, this person's so
smart ，查看他们实施的算法，或者这是一个很酷的 UI。
smart, look at this algorithm they
implemented, or this is a really cool UI.
也许没那么多
Probably not as much.
我推荐的是 GitHub
What I recommend is, yeah, have a GitHub,
有一些东西显示你可以编码，并且展示你的编码风格。
have something on there that shows you
can code, and shows your style of coding.
然后，加入 Twitter。
And then, join Twitter.
把你做的事都公布出来
Post out some of the things you do.
把它写在代码笔里，说我的这个动画让我很酷。
Post it in a code pen and say here's
this animation of me doing cool stuff.
我不能保证你会给你一份工作但你会注意到的
I can't guarantee you that's gonna land
you a job, but it'll get you noticed.
我要说的另一件事就是你要做的就是
Another thing I'd say is what
you absolutely have to do is you
必须网络。
have to network.
我知道我知道
I know.
我上大学的时候我很聪明我有个 CS 学位
When I was in college, I'm like,
I'm so smart, I got a CS degree,
所有人都要雇用我
everybody's gonna hire me.
然后什么也没做
And then nothing.
因为我是谁
Because who was I?
我只是另一个大学毕业生
I was just another college graduate.
但我做的是我交了朋友
But what I did was, I made friends.
我的第一份工作是我室友因为他在启动时有职位
I got my first job via my roommate
because he had a position at the startup
他当时在
he was at.
他就像在找一个兼职的人
And he's like hey, they're looking for
a junior part-time person.
他们是否利用我薪水很低的优势
And were they taking advantage
of me with very low pay?
可能吧
Probably.
但我在乎吗
But did I care?
不它让我体验了它让我在门口
No, it got me experience,
it got me in the door, and
我的简历里有我可以告诉人们的东西
it got something on my resume
that I can tell people about.
那是另一个吉姆的小费
And that's another Jim tip.
别在第一份工作上找围栏
Don't swing for
the fences on the first job.
你没有经验
You have no experiences.
您可能已在 Google 或 LinkedIn 或
You may have heard people at Google or
LinkedIn or
FrontendMasters 每年支付 200，000 美元，或作为前端工程师。
FrontendMasters getting paid $200,000 a
year or something as front end engineers.
这不会是你第一次出去
That's not gonna be your first time out.
除非你真的很出色真的很幸运
Unless you are truly exceptional and
get really, really, really lucky.
你开始时可能要付很低的工资
You're probably gonna take a pretty
low pay when you start off.
这只是没有经验的性质。
That's just the nature
of having no experience.
但确保你利用身边的人
But make sure you take advantage
of the people around you.
利用时间来学习。
Leverage the time to learn.
利用所有知识和一切可以从工作中获得的东西。
Leverage all the knowledge and
things you can get out of this job.
怎么了
Yes?
>> Online，有几个建议。
&gt;&gt; Online, there's a few suggestions.
个人项目，为开放式源代码提供帮助，以及
Personal projects,
contributing to open source, and
志愿组织了一个非政府组织的编码
volunteering coding for an NGO.
> > 嗯，这些都是实心的。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, those are all solid, too.
我唯一的问题是有人说 GitHub 是个开源的
My only issue with people saying yeah,
have a GitHub, contribute to open source,
所有这些都是你要以某种方式利用这个工作的
and all these things, is you have to
leverage that into a job somehow.
否则你就有点工作了
Otherwise you're kind of doing work.
我建议的最强的一个是联网。
The strongest one I always
recommend is networking.
网络，网络，网络。
Network, network, network.
他们不应该在大学教你，他们应该这样做。
It's unpleasant, they don't teach
it to you in college, they should.
但你必须了解认识人的人
But you have to know
people who know people.
交个朋友就好
And just make friends.
它只是向你展示他们想合作的人
It just shows you the type
person they wanna work with.
我在 Netflix 上的工作是在一个开始工作
How I got my job at Netflix was
I was working at a start up and
我申请了一次会议我也参加了
I applied to a conference, and I got in.
然后，我给了一个关于 React的演讲， EX6 ，并不重要。
And then, I gave a talk on React,
EX6, and doesn't really matter.
但事实证明我未来的老板也在场
But it turns out, my future boss
was there at the conference.
我想和这家伙谈谈
Like hey, I wanna talk to this guy.
他好像是个人
He seems like a personable person.
你可以通过我的演讲来告诉我的性格。
You can tell my personality
by how I give talks.
然后，这变成了一种应用，最终变成了一份工作。
And then, that turned into an application,
and that turned into a job eventually.
所以去参加会议，去 meetups ，和人们交谈。
So go to conferences,
go to meetups, talk to people.
网络，网络，网络，网络。
And network, network, network, network.
事实上，真实的故事，我有很多真实的故事。
In fact, real story, and
I have plenty of real stories.
这次研讨会的部分准备工作是我在一些地方申请工作。
Part of the preparation for this workshop
is I applied for jobs at places.
我没从招聘者中找到
I didn't get reached out from recruiters.
我尝试过我的简历和我所做的事我的演讲
I just tried to, with my resume and
the things I've done, and my talks and
这些都是我申请的工作
workshops and all that,
I applied for jobs.
你知道有多少人对我有反应吗
Do you know how many
people responded to me?
零没有人
Zero, nobody.
我申请了亚马逊的一份工作
I applied for a job at Amazon.
他们从来没有回来过我
They never got back to me.
我不是说我是世界上最伟大的工程师
And I'm not saying I'm
the world's greatest engineer.
可能连世界第二大工程师都没说
Probably not even saying the world's
second greatest engineer.
第三次
Third?
也许吧不
Maybe, no.
事实上，他们有成千上万的人。
The fact is they get thousands and
thousands of people.
如果你不符合他们的算法和准则
And if you don't match whatever
their algorithm or criteria is,
你可能就该过去了
you're probably just
gonna get passed over.
所以真正的方法是交朋友
So the real way to do it
is to make friends or
就跟在亚马逊在推特上工作的人一样
just follow someone who
works at Amazon on Twitter.
然后你就有了互动
And then eventually you
have a interaction.
我不是说这只是操控性的
And I don't mean this to be manipulative,
but
与人们建立真正的互动。
establish a genuine
interaction with people.
然后说嘿你给我开了规矩我在找
And then, say hey,
you got me open rules, I'm looking?
几乎所有人都会帮你
And almost everybody will help you out.
有人要求把它交给 Netflix
Anybody that's ever asked for
a referral to Netflix,
我从来没帮过他们
I've never not helped them out.
这并不是真正能帮你的工作
It's not really gonna help you
[LAUGH] that's not the way we work.
但我会一直帮你的
But I will always help you out.
我想大多数人会在社区里
I think most people will in the community.
我们都是好人
We're all generally good people.
我们理解想要找到新工作的感觉。
We understand what it's like
to try to find a new job.
我再说一次
So I'll say that again.
网络，网络，会面和会谈。
Network, network, meet-ups, and talks.
是的如果你没有经验你就该这么做
Yes, that's what you should
do if you have no experience.
还有一个网页。
And also have a web page.
我要知道你能做什么
I need to know what you can do.
最后的建议对我来说有点不满，卡兹我不是一个粉丝。
And this last piece of advice is a bit
distasteful for me, cuz I'm not a fan.
但我和很多招聘经理谈过
But I talk to a lot of hiring managers,
and
他们说你需要一个 LinkedIn 档案
they said you need to
have a LinkedIn profile.
它应该列出你的工作地点，以及你的技能。
And it should list where you've worked and
what are your skills.
你必须得 这是他们找到的主要方法之一
You have to.
That's one of the primary ways they find
人们是 LinkedIn。
people is LinkedIn.
这是我个人的意见，我不是太狂野，
This is my personal opinion,
I'm not too wild about it,
界面有点笨重的
the interface is kind of clunky.
但这些都是我们作为专业人士所须做的事情。
But these are things we have
to do as professionals.
因此，具有 LinkedIn 概要文件，具有 Web 页面和网络。
So have a LinkedIn profile,
have a webpage, and network.
怎么了
Yes?
> > 也许吧，我想这是个问题
&gt;&gt; So maybe, I guess it's
a question what do you do with
你的经验不是与 CS 相关的吗
experience that you have
that's not CS related?
是否有一种方法可以应用于您的应用程序?
Is there a way to work it
into your application?
> > 是，那是- >> 还是完全忽略它 ?
&gt;&gt; Yes, and that's-
&gt;&gt; Or do you just ignore it completely?
> > 不，那是个大问题。
&gt;&gt; No, no, that's a great question.
我放的，你还能看到我的简历，我有很多经验
What I put, and you can see it even on
my resume, is I have a lot of experience
在我之前的生活中做过软件工程师
from my previous life before
being a software engineer.
因此，我列举了我的专业经验。
So I list my professional
experience there.
所以这意味着它不是完全包含我所做的一切。
So that means it's not it's not entirely
encompassing of everything I've ever done.
但当你和某人坐下来说嘿
But when you sit down with someone and
you say hey,
你有管理人员的经验你就像我一样
do you have experience managing people,
you're like yes, I did.
我在一个主题公园里管理了几年的人。
I managed people at a theme park
through college for a couple of years.
所以在那里工作
So work it in there.
但在你的 LinkedIn 上，除非你把我的经验
But on your LinkedIn, probably leave out
the less relevant experience unless you
真的觉得很关键
really feel it's critical.